[
    {
        "Question": "dangle",
        "Answer": "hang",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "daring",
        "Answer": "bold",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "debate",
        "Answer": "argue",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "deceiving",
        "Answer": "misleading",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "decide",
        "Answer": "determine",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "decisive",
        "Answer": "determining",
        "Options": "definite"
    },
    {
        "Question": "declining",
        "Answer": "weakening",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "decorating",
        "Answer": "ornamental",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "deficiencies",
        "Answer": "shortages",
        "Options": "inadequate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "defining",
        "Answer": "important",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "deflect",
        "Answer": "redirect",
        "Options": "turn from its direction of movement"
    },
    {
        "Question": "degree",
        "Answer": "extent",
        "Options": "measure"
    },
    {
        "Question": "deliberate",
        "Answer": "careful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "deliberations",
        "Answer": "discussions",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "delicate",
        "Answer": "dainty",
        "Options": "fragile"
    },
    {
        "Question": "delicately",
        "Answer": "finely",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "delight",
        "Answer": "please",
        "Options": "pleasure"
    },
    {
        "Question": "deluxe",
        "Answer": "lavish",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "demanded",
        "Answer": "required",
        "Options": "needed"
    },
    {
        "Question": "demise",
        "Answer": "extinction",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "demonstrate",
        "Answer": "indicate",
        "Options": "show"
    },
    {
        "Question": "dense",
        "Answer": "thick",
        "Options": "more crowded"
    },
    {
        "Question": "dependable",
        "Answer": "reliable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "depicts",
        "Answer": "portrays",
        "Options": "pictured"
    },
    {
        "Question": "deposit",
        "Answer": "accumulate",
        "Options": "lay down"
    },
    {
        "Question": "derive",
        "Answer": "gain",
        "Options": "obtain"
    },
    {
        "Question": "desiccated",
        "Answer": "dry",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "design",
        "Answer": "create",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "designate",
        "Answer": "assign",
        "Options": "identify"
    },
    {
        "Question": "desolate",
        "Answer": "deserted",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "despite",
        "Answer": "even though",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "detach",
        "Answer": "separate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "detect",
        "Answer": "find",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "detected",
        "Answer": "discovered/ identified",
        "Options": "noticed/ revealed"
    },
    {
        "Question": "deter ",
        "Answer": "stop",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "deteriorated",
        "Answer": "got worse",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "determinants",
        "Answer": "causes",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "detractor",
        "Answer": "critic",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "detrimental",
        "Answer": "harmful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "devastate",
        "Answer": "destroy/ ruin",
        "Options": "extremely destructive"
    },
    {
        "Question": "deviate",
        "Answer": "detract",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "devised",
        "Answer": "created",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "devoid of",
        "Answer": "short of/ lack of",
        "Options": "without"
    },
    {
        "Question": "devoted",
        "Answer": "dedicated",
        "Options": "concentrated"
    },
    {
        "Question": "devour",
        "Answer": "eat",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dicimate",
        "Answer": "destroy",
        "Options": "destruct"
    },
    {
        "Question": "dictate",
        "Answer": "determine",
        "Options": "order"
    },
    {
        "Question": "differing",
        "Answer": "varying",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "diffuse",
        "Answer": "spread",
        "Options": "disperse"
    },
    {
        "Question": "dilemma",
        "Answer": "problem",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "diligent",
        "Answer": "careful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dilute",
        "Answer": "reduce",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dim",
        "Answer": "decrease",
        "Options": "weak"
    },
    {
        "Question": "dimension",
        "Answer": "aspect",
        "Options": "size"
    },
    {
        "Question": "disassemble",
        "Answer": "break up",
        "Options": "break apart"
    },
    {
        "Question": "disband",
        "Answer": "dismiss",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "discard",
        "Answer": "throw away",
        "Options": "throw up"
    },
    {
        "Question": "discernible",
        "Answer": "noticeable",
        "Options": "discriminating"
    },
    {
        "Question": "discharge",
        "Answer": "release",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "discipline",
        "Answer": "punish",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "discrete",
        "Answer": "separate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "disentangle",
        "Answer": "disband",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "disguised",
        "Answer": "hidden",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "disgust",
        "Answer": "distaste",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "diminished",
        "Answer": "reduced",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "discern",
        "Answer": "identify",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dismantle",
        "Answer": "demolish",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dismiss",
        "Answer": "reject",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "disorder",
        "Answer": "anarchy",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dispensable",
        "Answer": "not necessary",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dispersed",
        "Answer": "scattered",
        "Options": "spread"
    },
    {
        "Question": "displace",
        "Answer": "move out of position",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "disposition",
        "Answer": "temperament",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dispute",
        "Answer": "argument",
        "Options": "contention"
    },
    {
        "Question": "disruption",
        "Answer": "disturbance",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dissipate",
        "Answer": "disperse",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dissuade",
        "Answer": "discourage",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "distant",
        "Answer": "far",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "distinct",
        "Answer": "separate/ differ",
        "Options": "clear"
    },
    {
        "Question": "distinction",
        "Answer": "difference",
        "Options": "excellence"
    },
    {
        "Question": "distinctive",
        "Answer": "characteristic",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "distort",
        "Answer": "misinterpret",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "distributed",
        "Answer": "spread",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "distribution",
        "Answer": "geographic range",
        "Options": "dispersion"
    },
    {
        "Question": "disturb",
        "Answer": "upset",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "diversification",
        "Answer": "emergence of many varieties",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "diversified",
        "Answer": "varied",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "diverted",
        "Answer": "shifted",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "divest",
        "Answer": "deprive",
        "Options": "get rid of"
    },
    {
        "Question": "doctrine",
        "Answer": "principle",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "document",
        "Answer": "record",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "domain",
        "Answer": "field of expertise",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "domestic",
        "Answer": "household",
        "Options": "home"
    },
    {
        "Question": "dormant",
        "Answer": "inactive",
        "Options": "hibernated"
    },
    {
        "Question": "dramatic",
        "Answer": "striking",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dramatically",
        "Answer": "greatly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "drastically",
        "Answer": "extensively",
        "Options": "severely/ extremely"
    },
    {
        "Question": "drawbacks",
        "Answer": "disadvantages",
        "Options": "problem"
    },
    {
        "Question": "drawn to",
        "Answer": "attracted toward",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "drive",
        "Answer": "incentive",
        "Options": ""
    }
]